(Past Raj:)Okay, do you have an opinion
about everything?
(Leonard(voice off):)Yes.
(Past Howard:)You just assume you're always right?
(Past Sheldon:)It's not an assumption.
(Past Sheldon:)-Change seats with me.
-Why?
(Past Sheldon:)I don't like this spot.
I have to keep turning my head.
(Past Leonard:)Fine.
(Past Leonard:)It's time for Babylon 5.
(Past Sheldon:)We don't watch Babylon 5
in this apartment.
(Penny:)-Why not?
-Because no one likes Babylon 5.
(Past Leonard:)-I like it.
-Me too.
(Past Howard:)-So do I.
-There you go, three against one.
(Past Sheldon:)They don't get a vote. It's one against one.
(Past Sheldon:)And according to the roommate agreement,
all ties will be settled by me.
(Past Leonard:)-But I said no to that.
-And I said yes.
(Past Sheldon:)And I settle all ties.
(Past Sheldon:)-Change seats with me.
-Why?
(Past Sheldon:)There's a draft on my neck over here.
(Past Howard:)So I get the draft?
(Past Sheldon:)You're protected by your turtleneck.
(Past Leonard:)Fine.